http://www.createasoft.com/simulation-software-online-privacy-policy

Home
About CreateASoft, Inc.
Home
About CreateASoft, Inc.
Recent News
MODEX 2020 - Come visit us at Booth #7877 to experience Interactive Digital Twin Modeling in Virtual Reality using Simcad Pro 14.0. (Booth #7877) - March 9-12, 2020  •  Georgia World Congress Center  •  Atlanta, Georgia
Try out Simcad Pro Interactive VR - Modify and simulate the model in VR mode!
Winter Simulation Conference(WSC) 2019 - (Booth #31 & #32) - December 8-11 2019 - Gaylord National Resort & Convention Center - National Harbor, MD 20745
Association for Manafacturing Excellence(AME) Chicago 2019 - (Booth #305) - November 4-8, 2019 - Hyatt Regency Chicago
PROMAT 2019 - Supply Chain, Manufacturing, Distribution Trade Show - See Us at Booth #S3675 - April 8-11, 2019  •  McCormic Convention Center  •  Chicago, IL
MODEX 2018 - Supply Chain, Manufacturing, Distribution (Booth #B2346) - April 9-12, 2018  •  Georgia World Congress Center  •  Atlanta, Georgia
Stop by our Viewing Station and experience Simcad Pro Virtual Reality Simulation.
HEALTHCARE SYSTEMS PROCESS IMPROVEMENT CONFERENCE 2018 (Booth #201) - February 21-23, 2018  •  Grand Hyatt Atlanta  •  Atlanta, Georgia
ProMat 2017 - April 3-6, 2017 - Chicago's McCormick Place - CreateASoft Booth#: S3672
Healthcare Systems Process Improvement (HSPI) Conference 2017 - March 1-3, 2017 - Loews Royal Pacific Resort, Orlando, Florida - CreateASoft Booth#: 200
Stop by Booth #4 at WinterSim 2016 - December 11-14, Washington DC - for a preview of our Integrated Real-Time system powered by Dynamic Simulation - Download a copy of our presentation: REALTIME PREDICTIVE AND PRESCRIPTIVE ANALYTICS WITH REAL-TIME DATA AND SIMULATION
Visit us at MODEX 2016 - Booth #2531 April 4-7, 2016 - Georgia World Congress Center - Atlanta, GA
Healthcare Systems Process Improvement Conference 2016 - Booth #202 - Hilton Americas - Houston, Texas • Feb. 17-19, 2016
IIE 2015 ANNUAL Conference & Expo - Rensissance Nashville Hotel • May 30 - June 2, 2015 • Nashville, TN
HIMSS15 - HIMSS15 Intelligence Health Pavilion - April 12-16, 2015. Chicago, McCormick Place
ProMat 2015 - Chicago's McCormick Place - March 23-26, 2015.
2015 SHS - Society for Healthcare Systems - Orlando, FL - Feb 18-20, 2015.
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Process Simulator v11.4 - AURORA, IL – Dec 8, 2014
2014 Winter Simulation Conference - Savannah, GA - Dec 7-10, 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Process Simulator v11.3 - AURORA, IL – SEP 3, 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Introduces Simcad Pro Lite - Released and Available for Simulation - Aurora, Illinois – April 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Introduces Simcad Pro Health™ - Released and Available for Healthcare Simulation - Aurora, Illinois – March 2014
Recent Press Releases
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v14.1 and Simcad Pro Health v14.1 - AURORA, IL - Dec 1, 2020
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v14.0 and Simcad Pro Health v14.0 - AURORA, IL - Feb 3, 2020
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v13.3 - VR and Simcad Pro Health v13.3 - VR - AURORA, IL - July 15, 2019
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v13.2 - VR and Simcad Pro Health v13.2 - VR - AURORA, IL - January 4, 2019
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases "TruFit– Wearable fitting app Version 2.0" - AURORA, IL - December 20, 2018
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v13.1 - VR and Simcad Pro Health v13.1 - VR - AURORA, IL - September 20, 2018
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro v13.0 - VR and Simcad Pro Health v13.0 - VR - AURORA, IL - March 23, 2018
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro Dynamic Simulation Software and Simcad Pro Health v12.3 - AURORA, IL - May 4, 2017
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro Dynamic Simulation Software v12.2 - AURORA, IL - August 11, 2016
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro Dynamic Simulation Software v12.1 - AURORA, IL - May 6, 2016
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Pro Dynamic Simulation Software v12 - AURORA, IL - January 7, 2016
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Process Simulator v11.5 - AURORA, IL – May 18, 2015
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Process Simulator v11.4 - AURORA, IL – Dec 8, 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Releases Simcad Process Simulator v11.3 - AURORA, IL – SEPTEMBER 3, 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Introduces Simcad Pro Lite - Released and Available for Simulation - Aurora, Illinois – April 2014
CreateASoft, Inc. Introduces Simcad Pro Health™ - Designed Specifically for Healthcare Simulation - Aurora, Illinois – March 2014
Upcoming Events
Coming soon ...
Protecting privacy is always a CreateASoft priority. To underscore our fundamental commitment to privacy and our vision that good privacy is good business, we have adopted a online privacy policy for http://www.createasoft.com/. This policy reflects and implements---in an online setting---our corporate privacy principles and Fair Information Practice Principles of notice, choice, access, security, and accountability.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
I. Personal-identifiable information
This site only collects personal-identifiable information from you if you chose to provide this information to us. Personal-identifiable information collected with your consent may include, for example, name, e-mail address, resume information, or any inquires you may make through our web site. Create A Soft does not provide personal-identifiable information to unaffiliated third-parties in its normal course of business. However, we will provide such information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.
II. Cookies
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. This site uses third party cookies, however personally identifiable information is not collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are used to determine whether a visitor is unique or whether the visitor has viewed our site before. Cookies are optional and do not affect the operability of our site.
While most browsers are set to accept cookies by default, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you before accepting them. Your browser manufacturer has information on changing the default setting for your specific browser.
III. Non-personal-identifiable information.
This site also collects non-personal-identifiable information. For example, as you browse this web site we may collect information about your visit, but not about you personally. Via web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit our site (e.g., Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, etc.). Our web site uses an outsourcing program, Site wise, to assist us in analyzing this data to better tailor our web site.
IV. Retention
We reserve the right to retain personal-identifiable information collected through this site for the length of our business relationship with you. In some cases, we will retain the information for a longer period if required to do so by law, regulation, or the Individual Reference Services Group Industry Principles.
INFORMATION USE AND CONSUMER CHOICE
The information collected by this web site is used only for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request, maintaining your account (if you have one), and for the administration, review and/or the improvement the content of our web sites.
We may contact you in response to your comments or inquiries, as part of the maintenance of your account with us (if you have one), or in order to complete a transaction that you requested.
If you decide that you do not want to receive further emails regarding your inquiry from Create A Soft, you can reply to the email or use the telephone number (630) 428-2850 with a request that we not continue to email you. We do not use outside data sources to enrich marketing data obtained online.
ONWARD TRANSFER
We may disclose information you provide to us to third parties in order to complete a transaction that you requested.
We may also outsource some tasks, including the operation of certain website functions, that require access to information you supply online. In such cases, however, we require that the companies acting on our behalf abide by our privacy policy and institute safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your information.
Finally, please note that we may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.
ACCESS AND CORRECTION
As an information company, we know the importance of accurate data. Therefore, we strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through this web site. Furthermore, we believe that the individual is invaluable in ensuring that data is complete and accurate. We will provide you with access to personally-identifiable information you provide through our web site for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our web site.
If you wish to correct any inaccurate information you have submitted to this site, please call (630) 428-2850 or send an e-mail to: privacy@createasoft.com.
SECURITY
We take steps to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally-identifiable information collected through this web site. We recognize the importance of security for all personally-identifiable information collected by our web site. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers.
Once we receive personally-identifiable information, we take steps to protect its security on our systems. In the event we request or transmit sensitive information, such as credit card information or Social Security Numbers, we use industry standard, secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption.
We strictly limit access to personally-identifiable information to those employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities. All employees are prohibited from "browsing" through our files and databases. We train our employees in the application of our need-to-know standard. We periodically audit for compliance with this standard and we impose penalties for any failure to comply with this standard.
POLICY CHANGES
We may revise this online privacy policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the web site.
Our Mission: Provide organizations with the required tools and know-how to ensure competitive advantage and sustainability in an ever-demanding world market.
Privacy Policy
Simulation White Papers
The Role of Dynamic Simulation in Process Improvement Initiatives
Decreasing Patient Wait Time And Increasing Operational Efficiency in The ED
Improving Hospital Efficiency with Dynamic Simulation
Improve Patient Wait Time and Increase Operational Efficiency in the ED / ER
Dynamic Simulation for Lab Optimization can Help Increase Efficiency
Improving Manufacturing Practices with Dynamic Simulation
Improving Logistics Efficiency with Dynamic Simulation & Analysis
Dynamic Simulation for Distribution Centers
REQUEST FREE SIMCAD PRO TRIAL
REQUEST A SIMTRACK DEMO
Contact Us
If you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact us.
© 1992-2020 CreateASoft, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
